<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Amanda Yokingco</title>
    <link>https://yokingco.github.io/home/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Amanda Yokingco</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 01:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yokingco.github.io/home/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Projects</title>
      <link>https://yokingco.github.io/home/blog/data-science-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yokingco.github.io/home/blog/data-science-projects/</guid>
      <description>This page is under construction. Check back soon for more updates on my current and previous projects.  STAC53H3: Applied Data Collection Project Title: The Association Between Systolic Blood Pressure and Various Demographic, Lifestyle, and Physiological Characteristics of the American Public: An Applied Statistical Analysis
Runners on a track. Photo by Steven Lelham.
 Read the report here.
This was a final project for my Applied Data Collection course. The objective of this project was to analyze the relationship between systolic blood pressure (SBP) and smoking exposure as well as build a linear regression model to predict average SBP from multiple exposure variables (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facilitated Study Group Materials</title>
      <link>https://yokingco.github.io/home/blog/fsg-materials/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yokingco.github.io/home/blog/fsg-materials/</guid>
      <description>Person studying alone. Photo by Philippe Bout.
 Since May 2019, I have served as a Facilitated Study Group (FSG) leader, and more recently a mentor, for Introductory Statistics and Organic Chemistry II courses.
As a facilitator, I was responsible for developing learning materials and facilitating weekly in-person or virtual collaborative and interactive sessions for 20-50 students. As a mentor, I supported new and returning facilitators through weekly check-ins, constructive feedback, performance observations, and coordination of monthly meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Film Photography</title>
      <link>https://yokingco.github.io/home/blog/film-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yokingco.github.io/home/blog/film-photography/</guid>
      <description>In 2016, I picked up a film camera. Over the years, I have accumulated lots of memories over film. I wanted a place for some of them to live. Enjoy!
2018 Winter Stations, Toronto.
 Cebu City, Philippines.
 2019 Toronto Pan Am Sports Centre, University of Toronto Scarborough Campus.
 Carcross, Yukon Territory.
 2020 Rouge Beach, Scarborough, Ontario.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
